Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT) Records UA032
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Student records, 1918 -- 2012; 1918 -- 2009; UA032.002; 38.9 Linear Feet
  - Kellen, Constance, 1944; UA032.002.101.00144 (Box 101)
  - Gilbert, Matilda Jane, 1944; UA032.002.101.00145 (Box 101)
  - Gove, Esther Allen, 1944; UA032.002.101.00146 (Box 101)
  - Green, Patricia Wentworth, 1944; UA032.002.101.00147 (Box 101)
  - Hamilton, Daun, 1944; UA032.002.101.00148 (Box 101)
  - Heather, Phyllis T., 1944; UA032.002.101.00149 (Box 101)
  - Hemsing, Adriana, 1944; UA032.002.101.00150 (Box 101)
  - Herlihy, Mary Eugenia (Jean), 1944; UA032.002.101.00151 (Box 101)
  - Higgins, Jeanette R., 1944; UA032.002.101.00152 (Box 101)
  - Hill, Barbara J., 1944; UA032.002.101.00153 (Box 101)
  - Hunter, Jane, 1944; UA032.002.101.00154 (Box 101)
  - Jacobson, Elaine Clare, 1944; UA032.002.101.00155 (Box 101)
  - Kelly, Lenore, 1944; UA032.002.101.00156 (Box 101)
  - Kramer, Virginia, 1944; UA032.002.101.00157 (Box 101)
  - Lee, Marian L., 1944; UA032.002.101.00158 (Box 101)
  - Little, Ruth M., 1944; UA032.002.101.00159 (Box 101)
  - Lowrey, Lillian S., 1944; UA032.002.101.00160 (Box 101)
  - Lufkin, Priscilla A., 1944; UA032.002.101.00161 (Box 101)
  - Lutz, Marion Louise, 1944; UA032.002.101.00162 (Box 101)
  - Marks, Bertha H., 1944; UA032.002.101.00163 (Box 101)
  - Marshall, Elizabeth Bryan, 1944; UA032.002.101.00164 (Box 101)
  - Fowler, Mary Lou, 1944; UA032.002.101.00165 (Box 101)
  - McInerny, Anne E., 1944; UA032.002.101.00166 (Box 101)
  - Merrill, Jane, 1944; UA032.002.101.00167 (Box 101)
  - Merrill, May, 1943; UA032.002.101.00168 (Box 101)
  - Minor, Helen, 1944; UA032.002.101.00169 (Box 101)
  - Mitchell, Ruth White (Mrs. William), 1944; UA032.002.101.00170 (Box 101)
  - Moody, Margery Joan, 1943; UA032.002.101.00171 (Box 101)
  - Moyer, Ethel F., 1944; UA032.002.101.00172 (Box 101)
  - Muir, Lola Lenhart, 1944; UA032.002.101.00173 (Box 101)
  - Nelson, Annette (Mrs. George J. Gibavic), 1944; UA032.002.101.00174 (Box 101)
  - Nevius, Mary Janet, 1944; UA032.002.101.00175 (Box 101)
  - Nichols, Elizabeth Mary, 1944; UA032.002.101.00176 (Box 101)
  - Noble, Nancy, 1944; UA032.002.101.00177 (Box 101)
  - Obershulte, Margery Marie, 1944; UA032.002.101.00178 (Box 101)
  - Ogden, Ann Harvey, 1944; UA032.002.101.00179 (Box 101)
  - Offutt, Jeanne, 1944; UA032.002.101.00180 (Box 101)
  - Pickup, Virginia (Mrs. Alfred Y. Durell), 1944; UA032.002.101.00181 (Box 101)
  - Rand, Katharine, 1944; UA032.002.101.00182 (Box 101)
  - Randall, Ruth E., 1944; UA032.002.101.00183 (Box 101)
  - Riehl, Anil, 1944; UA032.002.101.00184 (Box 101)
  - Robinson, Grata, 1944; UA032.002.101.00185 (Box 101)
  - Rogers, Mary Van Dusen, 1944; UA032.002.101.00186 (Box 101)
  - Sanborn, Beatrice N. (Mrs.), 1944; UA032.002.101.00187 (Box 101)
  - Sargent, Anna E., 1944; UA032.002.101.00188 (Box 101)
  - Seaton, Joan E., 1944; UA032.002.101.00189 (Box 101)
  - Shepard, Carol C., 1944; UA032.002.101.00190 (Box 101)
  - Smith, Carol F., 1944; UA032.002.101.00191 (Box 101)
  - Steglich, L. Ruth, 1944; UA032.002.101.00192 (Box 101)
  - Steitz, Charlotte Elise, 1944; UA032.002.101.00193 (Box 101)
  - Storr, Virginia V. (Mrs. Richard J.), 1944; UA032.002.101.00194 (Box 101)
  - Strassberger, Eleanor, 1944; UA032.002.101.00195 (Box 101)
  - Sullivan, Anne K., 1944; UA032.002.101.00196 (Box 101)
  - Swaim, Caroline, 1944; UA032.002.101.00197 (Box 101)
  - Sweetland, Elizabeth R., 1944; UA032.002.101.00198 (Box 101)
  - Tuttle, Jane, 1944; UA032.002.101.00199 (Box 101)
  - Turner, Carol R., 1944; UA032.002.101.00200 (Box 101)
  - Vose, Esther, 1944; UA032.002.101.00201 (Box 101)
  - Williamson, Barbara A., 1944; UA032.002.101.00202 (Box 101)
  - Williams, Ann Cartledge, 1944; UA032.002.101.00203 (Box 101)
  - Winter, Mary W., 1944; UA032.002.101.00204 (Box 101)
  - Wiswall, Nancy, 1944; UA032.002.101.00205 (Box 101)
  - Wolf, Louise, 1944; UA032.002.101.00206 (Box 101)
  - Wycoff, Juanita, 1944; UA032.002.101.00207 (Box 101)
  - Youmans, Jane S., 1944; UA032.002.101.00208 (Box 101)
  - Ziegler, Sarah J., 1944; UA032.002.101.00209 (Box 101)
  - Alberston, Eleanor T., 1945; UA032.002.102.00001 (Box 102)
  - Ames, Dorothy, 1945; UA032.002.102.00002 (Box 102)
  - Anderson, Astrid Genevieve, 1944; UA032.002.102.00003 (Box 102)
  - Ballou, Marion, 1945; UA032.002.102.00004 (Box 102)
  - Barnes, Marcia, 1945; UA032.002.102.00005 (Box 102)
  - Bauman, Anna Elizabeth, 1945; UA032.002.102.00006 (Box 102)
  - Benson, Mildred, 1945; UA032.002.102.00007 (Box 102)
  - Bingham, Margaret R., 1945; UA032.002.102.00008 (Box 102)
  - Bixby, Patricia Ruth, 1945; UA032.002.102.00009 (Box 102)
  - Bourget, Barbara H., 1945; UA032.002.102.00010 (Box 102)
  - Chase, Gladys D., 1945; UA032.002.102.00011 (Box 102)
  - Chellman, Dorothy, 1945; UA032.002.102.00012 (Box 102)
  - Cheney, Grace Hurd, 1945; UA032.002.102.00013 (Box 102)
  - Culbertson, Jean, 1945; UA032.002.102.00014 (Box 102)
  - Davis, Edith G., 1945; UA032.002.102.00015 (Box 102)
  - Dustin, Marcia, 1945; UA032.002.102.00016 (Box 102)
  - Fallon, Patricia, 1945; UA032.002.102.00017 (Box 102)
  - Hayes, Margery, 1945; UA032.002.102.00018 (Box 102)
  - Hedstrom, Sonja, 1945; UA032.002.102.00019 (Box 102)
  - Holifield, Lois, 1945; UA032.002.102.00020 (Box 102)
  - Jameson, Janet, 1945; UA032.002.102.00021 (Box 102)
  - Jenson, Inez M., 1945; UA032.002.102.00022 (Box 102)
  - Magee, Frances Elizabeth, 1945; UA032.002.102.00023 (Box 102)
  - Kalem, Theodora Frances Ellen, 1945; UA032.002.102.00024 (Box 102)
  - Kunz, Priscilla L., 1945; UA032.002.102.00025 (Box 102)
  - Lanigan, Kathryn E., 1945; UA032.002.102.00026 (Box 102)
  - Lawson, Betty Virginia, 1945; UA032.002.102.00027 (Box 102)
  - Madden, Kathryn Jeannette, 1945; UA032.002.102.00028 (Box 102)
  - Mills, Carolyn, 1945; UA032.002.102.00029 (Box 102)
  - Mudge, Anne Cushman, 1945; UA032.002.102.00030 (Box 102)
  - Nicholson, Oline Elizabeth, 1945; UA032.002.102.00031 (Box 102)
  - Ott, Marita Maxwell, 1945; UA032.002.102.00032 (Box 102)
  - Pierce, Dagmar L., 1945; UA032.002.102.00033 (Box 102)
  - Pratt, Mary Louise, 1945; UA032.002.102.00034 (Box 102)
  - Read, Naomi L., 1945; UA032.002.102.00035 (Box 102)
  - Ring, Eleanor (Mrs.), 1945; UA032.002.102.00036 (Box 102)
  - Robbins, Alice Marjorie, 1945; UA032.002.102.00037 (Box 102)
  - Robbins, Ethel, 1945; UA032.002.102.00038 (Box 102)
  - Sawyer, Janet Bryant, 1945; UA032.002.102.00039 (Box 102)
  - Scheu, Mary Lea, 1945; UA032.002.102.00040 (Box 102)
  - Smith, Jean Hayes, 1945; UA032.002.102.00041 (Box 102)
  - Stafford, Anne D., 1945; UA032.002.102.00042 (Box 102)
  - Taber, Frances D., 1945; UA032.002.102.00043 (Box 102)
  - Towner, Shirley Ann, 1945; UA032.002.102.00044 (Box 102)
  - VIets, Barbara, 1945; UA032.002.102.00045 (Box 102)
  - White, Marjory V., 1945; UA032.002.102.00046 (Box 102)
  - Williams, Barbara Anne, 1945; UA032.002.102.00047 (Box 102)
  - Wise, Olive E., 1945; UA032.002.102.00048 (Box 102)
  - Anty, Elizabeth, 1946; UA032.002.102.00049 (Box 102)
  - Barss, Helen, 1946; UA032.002.102.00050 (Box 102)
  - Bernt, Mary Elizabeth, 1946; UA032.002.102.00051 (Box 102)
  - Boyd, Martha, 1946; UA032.002.102.00052 (Box 102)
  - Carothers, Olivia, 1946; UA032.002.102.00053 (Box 102)
  - Cate, Eunice A., 1946; UA032.002.102.00054 (Box 102)
  - Chernewski, Eleanora, 1946; UA032.002.102.00055 (Box 102)
  - Chung-Hoon, Marie Philani, 1946; UA032.002.102.00056 (Box 102)
  - Clothier, Shirley, 1946; UA032.002.102.00057 (Box 102)
  - Cotter, Elizabeth (Mrs.), 1946; UA032.002.102.00058 (Box 102)
  - Cross, Ann, 1946; UA032.002.102.00059 (Box 102)
  - Cummings, Gladys, 1946; UA032.002.102.00060 (Box 102)
  - Decatur, Susan, 1946; UA032.002.102.00061 (Box 102)
  - Dounelis, Gloria Ann, 1946; UA032.002.102.00062 (Box 102)
  - Edwards, Betsy Ann, 1946; UA032.002.102.00063 (Box 102)
  - Franklin, Jane, 1946; UA032.002.102.00064 (Box 102)
  - Ferguson, Margaret C., 1946; UA032.002.102.00065 (Box 102)
  - Finerty, Patricia Anne, 1946; UA032.002.102.00066 (Box 102)
  - Forbes, Elizabeth S., 1946; UA032.002.102.00067 (Box 102)
  - Freelander, Jean, 1946; UA032.002.102.00068 (Box 102)
  - Frisselle, Jane Rowe (Mrs. George B. Glove), 1946; UA032.002.102.00069 (Box 102)
  - Gibbs, Kathryn Elizabeth, 1946; UA032.002.102.00070 (Box 102)
  - Grant, Josephine, 1945; UA032.002.102.00071 (Box 102)
  - Greene, Caroline, 1946; UA032.002.102.00072 (Box 102)
  - Grenwood, Phyllis Jeanette, 1946; UA032.002.102.00073 (Box 102)
  - Harkins, Barbara Ann, 1946; UA032.002.102.00074 (Box 102)
  - Harvey, Lois Jacqueline, 1946; UA032.002.102.00075 (Box 102)
  - Haussermann, Caroline, 1946; UA032.002.102.00076 (Box 102)
  - Hodgkins, Nancy, 1946; UA032.002.102.00077 (Box 102)
  - Hoffman, Edna R., 1946; UA032.002.102.00078 (Box 102)
  - Howes, Barbara, 1946; UA032.002.102.00079 (Box 102)
  - Jackson, Alice, 1946; UA032.002.102.00080 (Box 102)
  - Joyce, Patricia Mary, 1946; UA032.002.102.00081 (Box 102)
  - Kaplan, Estelle, 1946; UA032.002.102.00082 (Box 102)
  - Kendall, Bernice Alden, 1946; UA032.002.102.00083 (Box 102)
  - Kessler, Marilyn, 1946; UA032.002.102.00084 (Box 102)
  - Knapp, Judith, 1946; UA032.002.102.00085 (Box 102)
  - Krugelis, Bertha E., 1946; UA032.002.102.00086 (Box 102)
  - Lawson, Jessie D. (Mrs. A. W.), 1946; UA032.002.102.00087 (Box 102)
  - MacDougall, Leah Faith, 1945; UA032.002.102.00088 (Box 102)
  - MacGregor, Margaret E., 1946; UA032.002.102.00089 (Box 102)
  - Marsh, Deborah, 1946; UA032.002.102.00090 (Box 102)
  - Marsh, F. Evelyn, 1946; UA032.002.102.00091 (Box 102)
  - Morrison, Barbara (Mrs. Wesley B. Hill), 1946; UA032.002.102.00092 (Box 102)
  - McConnell, Dorothy LouVene, 1946; UA032.002.102.00093 (Box 102)
  - McCord, Joan H., 1946; UA032.002.102.00094 (Box 102)
  - McCrum, Ruth Cowle(s), 1946; UA032.002.102.00095 (Box 102)
  - Merrill, Phyllis, 1946; UA032.002.102.00096 (Box 102)
  - Miller, Louise, 1946; UA032.002.102.00097 (Box 102)
  - Murphy, Florence, 1946; UA032.002.102.00098 (Box 102)
  - Nadzeika, Julia B., 1946; UA032.002.102.00099 (Box 102)
  - Noren, June, 1946; UA032.002.102.00100 (Box 102)
  - O'Brien, Margaret (Ruth), 1946; UA032.002.102.00101 (Box 102)
  - Partridge, Adelaide, 1946; UA032.002.102.00102 (Box 102)
  - Peabody, Elizabeth, 1946; UA032.002.102.00103 (Box 102)
  - Pinkham, Elaine Sargent, 1945; UA032.002.102.00104 (Box 102)
  - Reddish, Suzanne, 1946; UA032.002.102.00105 (Box 102)
  - Richardson, Elinor Calvert, 1946; UA032.002.102.00106 (Box 102)
  - Rozinsky, Minna, 1946; UA032.002.102.00107 (Box 102)
  - Schaefer, Sally Jean, 1946; UA032.002.102.00108 (Box 102)
  - Sherwood, Theodosia, 1946; UA032.002.102.00109 (Box 102)
  - Smith, Mary Elizabeth, 1946; UA032.002.102.00110 (Box 102)
  - Smith, Rosamond, 1946; UA032.002.102.00111 (Box 102)
  - Steffanson, Elsa, 1946; UA032.002.102.00112 (Box 102)
  - Trowt, Mrs. Marion Elsie, 1946; UA032.002.102.00113 (Box 102)
  - Twiss, Priscilla, 1946; UA032.002.102.00114 (Box 102)
  - Van Wert, Helen A., 1946; UA032.002.102.00115 (Box 102)
  - Viets, Elizabeth Winthrop, 1946; UA032.002.102.00116 (Box 102)
  - Whittemore, Dorothy, 1946; UA032.002.102.00117 (Box 102)
  - Winslow, Barbara (Mrs. Calvin Hamilton), 1946; UA032.002.102.00118 (Box 102)
  - Wright, Claire, 1946; UA032.002.102.00119 (Box 102)
  - Zickell, Jean, 1946; UA032.002.102.00120 (Box 102)
  - Zintz, Dolores, 1946; UA032.002.102.00121 (Box 102)
  - Balcom, Nancy, 1947; UA032.002.102.00122 (Box 102)
  - Barton, Shirley, 1947; UA032.002.102.00123 (Box 102)
  - Baker, Melissa, 1947; UA032.002.102.00124 (Box 102)
  - Breed, Patricia Anne, 1947; UA032.002.102.00125 (Box 102)
  - Brock, Charity Jane, 1947; UA032.002.102.00126 (Box 102)
  - Cadbury, Catharine C., 1947; UA032.002.102.00127 (Box 102)
  - Chamberlain, Jeannette, 1947; UA032.002.102.00128 (Box 102)
  - Cone, Joan, 1947; UA032.002.102.00129 (Box 102)
  - Crosby, Joanne, 1947; UA032.002.102.00130 (Box 102)
  - Damon, Patricia, 1947; UA032.002.102.00131 (Box 102)
  - Duckworth, Gillian Alisan, 1947; UA032.002.102.00132 (Box 102)
  - Duehring, Marcia, 1947; UA032.002.102.00133 (Box 102)
  - Edlund, Esther, 1947; UA032.002.102.00134 (Box 102)
  - Elman, G. Trudence, 1947; UA032.002.102.00135 (Box 102)
  - Fenn, Ruth, 1947; UA032.002.102.00136 (Box 102)
  - Forde, Priscilla, 1947; UA032.002.102.00137 (Box 102)
  - Fowler, Jane M., 1947; UA032.002.102.00138 (Box 102)
  - Fowler, Janet, 1947; UA032.002.102.00139 (Box 102)
  - Gardner, Marietta, 1947; UA032.002.102.00140 (Box 102)
  - Gauchat, Joan, 1947; UA032.002.102.00141 (Box 102)
  - Goehring, Jane, 1947; UA032.002.102.00142 (Box 102)
  - Goldflies, Marian, 1947; UA032.002.102.00143 (Box 102)
  - Hackett, Hazel, 1947; UA032.002.102.00144 (Box 102)
  - Harrison, Eleanor, 1947; UA032.002.102.00145 (Box 102)
  - Hewitt, Berenice, 1947; UA032.002.102.00146 (Box 102)
  - Howes, Ruth, 1947; UA032.002.102.00147 (Box 102)
  - Hubbard, Janice (Mrs. Carl Rushford), 1947; UA032.002.102.00148 (Box 102)
  - Huntington, Alice, 1947; UA032.002.102.00149 (Box 102)
  - Hussey, Alice, 1947; UA032.002.102.00150 (Box 102)
  - Ingersoll, Geraldine R. (Mrs. Herbert V.), 1947; UA032.002.102.00151 (Box 102)
  - Klein, Enid, 1947; UA032.002.102.00152 (Box 102)
  - Johnston, Marguerite M., 1947; UA032.002.102.00153 (Box 102)
  - Lebow, Grace (Hackel), 1947; UA032.002.102.00154 (Box 102)
  - Lothrop, Margaret, 1947; UA032.002.102.00155 (Box 102)
  - Mateer, Mary, 1947; UA032.002.102.00156 (Box 102)
  - Mills, Emily, 1947; UA032.002.102.00157 (Box 102)
  - Mosher, Elinor, 1947; UA032.002.102.00158 (Box 102)
  - Perlot, Marjorie, 1947; UA032.002.102.00159 (Box 102)
  - Perrin, Joan, 1947; UA032.002.102.00160 (Box 102)
  - Pierce, Katherine, 1947; UA032.002.102.00161 (Box 102)
  - Ravreby, Marcia, 1950; UA032.002.102.00162 (Box 102)
  - Ricker, Barbara, 1947; UA032.002.102.00163 (Box 102)
  - Russell, Carol T., 1947; UA032.002.102.00164 (Box 102)
  - Smith, Virgina W., 1947; UA032.002.102.00165 (Box 102)
  - Snow, Beryl, 1947; UA032.002.102.00166 (Box 102)
  - Spang, Barbara, 1947; UA032.002.102.00167 (Box 102)
  - Spooner, Lois Elaine, 1947; UA032.002.102.00168 (Box 102)
  - Sushel, Florence, 1947; UA032.002.102.00169 (Box 102)
  - Thorpe, Betty E., 1947; UA032.002.102.00170 (Box 102)
  - Trowbridge, Anne L., 1947; UA032.002.102.00171 (Box 102)
  - Tunison, Cynthia, 1947; UA032.002.102.00172 (Box 102)
  - Twitchell, Shirley, 1947; UA032.002.102.00173 (Box 102)
  - Weaver, Sonia (Mrs. Robert A.), 1947; UA032.002.102.00174 (Box 102)
  - Weeks, Martha, 1947; UA032.002.102.00175 (Box 102)
  - Wheeler, Polly, 1947; UA032.002.102.00176 (Box 102)
  - Wood, Eleanor J., 1947; UA032.002.102.00177 (Box 102)
  - Woodman, Judith, 1947; UA032.002.102.00178 (Box 102)
  - Alvord, Bertha I. (Lieut. USNR), 1948; UA032.002.102.00179 (Box 102)
  - Ball, Mary June, 1952; UA032.002.102.00180 (Box 102)
  - Benson, Anna J. (Lt. Cmdr. USN), 1948; UA032.002.102.00181 (Box 102)
  - Brinkler, Vera H., 1948; UA032.002.102.00182 (Box 102)
  - Caldwell, Helen Ward (Lieut. USN), 1948; UA032.002.102.00183 (Box 102)
  - Collins, Glendore (Lt. Cmdr. USN), 1948; UA032.002.102.00184 (Box 102)
  - Earl, Louise (Lieut. USNR), 1948; UA032.002.102.00185 (Box 102)
  - Furcheimer, Ilse Schemy, 1948; UA032.002.102.00186 (Box 102)
  - Kelley, Leah G. (Lieut. USN), 1948; UA032.002.102.00187 (Box 102)
  - Kieler, Lydia R. (Lieut. USNR), 1948; UA032.002.102.00188 (Box 102)
  - Lachowicz, Zofia, 1948; UA032.002.102.00189 (Box 102)
  - Leeming, Avery, 1948; UA032.002.102.00190 (Box 102)
  - Russell, Martha, 1948; UA032.002.102.00191 (Box 102)
  - McClatchey, Olive G. (Lieut. USNR), 1948; UA032.002.102.00192 (Box 102)
  - Morin, Aline E. (Ensign USNR), 1948; UA032.002.102.00193 (Box 102)
  - Munroe, Barbara (Lieut. USN), 1948; UA032.002.102.00194 (Box 102)
  - Naviaux, Dorothy A. (Lieut. USNR), 1948; UA032.002.102.00195 (Box 102)
  - Nesgis, Rosella (Lt. Cmdr. USN), 1948; UA032.002.102.00196 (Box 102)
  - Neeson, Marilyn Fay, 1948; UA032.002.102.00197 (Box 102)
  - Newhall, Mary, 1948; UA032.002.102.00198 (Box 102)
  - Norris, Martha I., 1948; UA032.002.102.00199 (Box 102)
  - Overton, Minne (Lt. Comdr. USN), 1948; UA032.002.102.00200 (Box 102)
  - Pace, Barbara, 1948; UA032.002.102.00201 (Box 102)
  - Harris, Natalie R. (Mrs. Paul Riffin), 1948; UA032.002.102.00202 (Box 102)
  - Rodriguez, Nydia, 1948; UA032.002.102.00203 (Box 102)
  - Sacarny, Elaine (Mrs. Julius Zack), 1948; UA032.002.102.00204 (Box 102)
  - Schwartz, Marie M. (Lieut. USN), 1948; UA032.002.102.00205 (Box 102)
  - Swift, Lorita B. (Lt. Comdr. USN), 1948; UA032.002.102.00206 (Box 102)
  - White, Jean Searles, 1948; UA032.002.102.00207 (Box 102)
  - Andrews, Gyneve, 1949; UA032.002.102.00208 (Box 102)
  - Arnold, Mary Susan, 1949; UA032.002.102.00209 (Box 102)
  - Burke, Virginia, 1949; UA032.002.102.00210 (Box 102)
  - Chandler, Marjorie, 1949; UA032.002.102.00211 (Box 102)
  - Aronson, Irma (Cohen, Mrs. George), 1949; UA032.002.102.00212 (Box 102)
  - Duffy, Eleanor Margaret, 1949; UA032.002.102.00213 (Box 102)
  - Dunmore, Barbara, 1949; UA032.002.102.00214 (Box 102)
  - Fonseca, Maria Elena, 1949; UA032.002.102.00215 (Box 102)
  - Gardner, Patricia (Mrs. Charles Poirier), 1949; UA032.002.102.00216 (Box 102)
  - Gordon, Mary E., 1949; UA032.002.102.00217 (Box 102)
  - Graf, Mrs. Alfred, 1949; UA032.002.102.00218 (Box 102)
  - Grove, Mary Ellen (Ensign USNR) (Mrs. A. R. McLain), 1948; UA032.002.102.00219 (Box 102)
  - Hammond, Nancy, 1949; UA032.002.102.00220 (Box 102)
  - Hay, Janet M. (Mrs. William D. McGuigan), 1948; UA032.002.102.00221 (Box 102)
  - Hellmers, Ann Sherman, 1948; UA032.002.102.00222 (Box 102)
  - Howe, Patricia, 1948; UA032.002.102.00223 (Box 102)
  - Ide, Rhoda J., 1949; UA032.002.102.00224 (Box 102)
  - Jenkins, Evelyn E. (Lieut. USN), 1948; UA032.002.102.00225 (Box 102)
  - Kelley, Patricia, 1949; UA032.002.102.00226 (Box 102)
  - Lonsbury, Barbara Ann, 1951; UA032.002.102.00227 (Box 102)
  - Maddox, Rena, 1952; UA032.002.102.00228 (Box 102)
  - Massa, Lorraine Harume, 1949; UA032.002.102.00229 (Box 102)
  - McLaughlin, Mariana V., 1949; UA032.002.102.00230 (Box 102)
  - Morton, Elizabeth, 1949; UA032.002.102.00231 (Box 102)
  - Phillips, Emily Ruth, 1949; UA032.002.102.00232 (Box 102)
  - Piper, Bertha, J., 1949; UA032.002.102.00233 (Box 102)
  - Pyburn, Jeanette, 1949; UA032.002.102.00234 (Box 102)
  - Robinson, Patrica F., 1949; UA032.002.102.00235 (Box 102)
  - Rodger, Barbara B., 1949; UA032.002.102.00236 (Box 102)
  - Rogolsky, Marion, 1949; UA032.002.102.00237 (Box 102)
  - Rushton, Norma, 1949; UA032.002.102.00238 (Box 102)
  - Slobins, Phyllis (Mrs. Maxwell Cohen), 1949; UA032.002.102.00239 (Box 102)
  - Small, Evelyn A., 1949; UA032.002.102.00240 (Box 102)
  - Spear, Marilyn Elaine, 1949; UA032.002.102.00241 (Box 102)
  - Thayer, Patricia, 1949; UA032.002.102.00242 (Box 102)
  - Waghorne, Anne, 1949; UA032.002.102.00243 (Box 102)
  - Waldman, Barbara Lois, 1949; UA032.002.102.00244 (Box 102)
  - Williams, Druzilla Bradford (Mrs. Henry Schock), 1949; UA032.002.102.00245 (Box 102)
  - Wilkes, Rose C., 1949; UA032.002.102.00246 (Box 102)
  - Andrews, Jeralyn Jane, 1950; UA032.002.103.00001 (Box 103)
  - Bacheller, Marilyn, 1950; UA032.002.103.00002 (Box 103)
  - Boland, Mary Elizabeth, 1950; UA032.002.103.00003 (Box 103)
  - Bradley, Patricia Anne, 1950; UA032.002.103.00004 (Box 103)
  - Bragdon, Marjorie, 1950; UA032.002.103.00005 (Box 103)
  - Brown, Marcia Mary, 1950; UA032.002.103.00006 (Box 103)
  - Bruce, Ruth L., 1950; UA032.002.103.00007 (Box 103)
  - Campbell, Catherine, special blind student, 1950; UA032.002.103.00008 (Box 103)
  - Dalton, Ruth, 1950; UA032.002.103.00009 (Box 103)
  - Dea, Allison, 1950; UA032.002.103.00010 (Box 103)
  - Depue, Margaret Van Nostrand, 1950; UA032.002.103.00011 (Box 103)
  - Eaton, Elizabeth, 1950; UA032.002.103.00012 (Box 103)
  - Elliott, Rose Meredith, 1950; UA032.002.103.00013 (Box 103)
  - Ellis, Martha, 1950; UA032.002.103.00014 (Box 103)
  - Foote, Madeline Bartol, 1950; UA032.002.103.00015 (Box 103)
  - Goselin, Jean, 1950; UA032.002.103.00016 (Box 103)
  - Groner, Sally Anne, 1950; UA032.002.103.00017 (Box 103)
  - Hill, Audrey, 1950; UA032.002.103.00018 (Box 103)
  - Hill, Marion F., 1950; UA032.002.103.00019 (Box 103)
  - HIllson, Elaine, 1950; UA032.002.103.00020 (Box 103)
  - Hopkins, Joan, 1950; UA032.002.103.00021 (Box 103)
  - Hubbell, Eleanore, 1950; UA032.002.103.00022 (Box 103)
  - Hull, Lila R., 1950; UA032.002.103.00023 (Box 103)
  - Lawson, Roberta Stone (Mrs. William M. Simpson), 1950; UA032.002.103.00024 (Box 103)
  - Leve, Fredda A., 1950; UA032.002.103.00025 (Box 103)
  - Kavanaugh, Marguerite, 1950; UA032.002.103.00026 (Box 103)
  - Kent, Roberta Lane, 1950; UA032.002.103.00027 (Box 103)
  - Kezar, Beverly L., 1950; UA032.002.103.00028 (Box 103)
  - Morrow, Susan Catherine, 1950; UA032.002.103.00029 (Box 103)
  - Murphy, Mary-Alice, 1950; UA032.002.103.00030 (Box 103)
  - O'Brien, Elizabeth A., 1950; UA032.002.103.00031 (Box 103)
  - Orcutt, Constance, 1950; UA032.002.103.00032 (Box 103)
  - O'Shea, Jane (Mrs. John E. Stanick), 1950; UA032.002.103.00033 (Box 103)
  - Reade, Margaret, 1950; UA032.002.103.00034 (Box 103)
  - Rogers, Carolyn, 1950; UA032.002.103.00035 (Box 103)
  - Rogers, Jane, 1950; UA032.002.103.00036 (Box 103)
  - Roorbach, Jean, 1950; UA032.002.103.00037 (Box 103)
  - Sinclair, Mrs. Lois, 1950; UA032.002.103.00038 (Box 103)
  - Laurentanta, Sister Mary, 1950; UA032.002.103.00039 (Box 103)
  - Sloan, Mary Elaine, 1950; UA032.002.103.00040 (Box 103)
  - Stadepole, Nancy, 1950; UA032.002.103.00041 (Box 103)
  - Steele, Joanne Elizabeth, 1950; UA032.002.103.00042 (Box 103)
  - Stewart, Marjorie Deane, 1950; UA032.002.103.00043 (Box 103)
  - Swenson, Harriet, 1950; UA032.002.103.00044 (Box 103)
  - Thompson, Theodosia, 1950; UA032.002.103.00045 (Box 103)
  - Wade, Joan, 1950; UA032.002.103.00046 (Box 103)
  - Webb, Hazel, 1950; UA032.002.103.00047 (Box 103)
  - Weston, Marian June, 1950; UA032.002.103.00048 (Box 103)
  - White, Muriel, 1949; UA032.002.103.00049 (Box 103)
  - Aldrich, Deborah Ann, 1951; UA032.002.103.00050 (Box 103)
  - Belyea, Robert Edward, 1951; UA032.002.103.00051 (Box 103)
  - Berman, Barbara Louise, 1951; UA032.002.103.00052 (Box 103)
  - Boulton, Marcia Howard, 1951; UA032.002.103.00053 (Box 103)
  - Brooks, Barbara Ann, 1951; UA032.002.103.00054 (Box 103)
  - Bunker, Laurel Gladys, 1951; UA032.002.103.00055 (Box 103)
  - Caner, Emily, 1951; UA032.002.103.00056 (Box 103)
  - Carver, Elizabeth Mary, 1951; UA032.002.103.00057 (Box 103)
  - Caplan, Marcia, 1951; UA032.002.103.00058 (Box 103)
  - Cook, Dora L. (Mrs. John R. Freeburn), 1951; UA032.002.103.00059 (Box 103)
  - Craig, Jean Mansfield, 1951; UA032.002.103.00060 (Box 103)
  - Davis, Eunice Jean, 1951; UA032.002.103.00061 (Box 103)
  - Elliott, Jean, 1951; UA032.002.103.00062 (Box 103)
  - Fiorentino, Mary R., 1951; UA032.002.103.00063 (Box 103)
  - Fossati, Jean Marie, 1951; UA032.002.103.00064 (Box 103)
  - Griselle, Suzanne, 1951; UA032.002.103.00065 (Box 103)
  - Hill, Nancy Lee, 1951; UA032.002.103.00066 (Box 103)
  - Holland, Miss Shirley Jean (Mrs. Ramon Carr), 1951; UA032.002.103.00067 (Box 103)
  - Hull, Laura Anne (Rockell, Mrs. Dwight L.), 1951; UA032.002.103.00068 (Box 103)
  - Jolly, Elayne Louise, 1951; UA032.002.103.00069 (Box 103)
  - Jones, Elsie Marie (Mrs.), 1951; UA032.002.103.00070 (Box 103)
  - Kaplan, Harriet Diana, 1951; UA032.002.103.00071 (Box 103)
  - Kissileff, Betty Lee, 1951; UA032.002.103.00072 (Box 103)
  - Kistler, Dorothy (Padgett), 1951; UA032.002.103.00073 (Box 103)
  - Leamon, Sylvia, 1951; UA032.002.103.00074 (Box 103)
  - MacBride, Muriel R., 1951; UA032.002.103.00075 (Box 103)
  - Markson, Rhoda A., 1951; UA032.002.103.00076 (Box 103)